<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><RECORD>
   <GOID>220045304</GOID>
   
   <Obj>
      <SourceRollupType>Newspapers</SourceRollupType>
      <ObjectTypes>
         <other ObjectTypeOrigin="Publisher">News</other>
         <mstar>News</mstar>
      </ObjectTypes>
      <ObjectRollupType>Articles - All Types</ObjectRollupType>
      <TitleAtt>
         <Title>National League notes</Title>
      </TitleAtt>
      <SubTitleAtt>
         <SubTitle>[1]</SubTitle>
      </SubTitleAtt>
      <NumericDate>2010-04-28</NumericDate>
      <StartDate>2010-04-28</StartDate>
      <EndDate>2010-04-28</EndDate>
      <AlphaDate>Apr 28, 2010</AlphaDate>
      <Language>
         <RawLang>English</RawLang>
      </Language>
      <Language IsPrimary="true">
         <ISO>
            <ISOCode>ENG</ISOCode>
            <ISOExpansion ISOCode="ENG">English</ISOExpansion>
         </ISO>
      </Language>
      <Copyright>
         <CopyrightData>(Copyright (c) 2010 USA Today. All Rights Reserved.)</CopyrightData>
      </Copyright>
      <PrintLocation>
         <StartPage>C.5</StartPage>
         <Pagination>C.5</Pagination>
         <DocSection>SPORTS</DocSection>
         <DocEdition>FINAL</DocEdition>
      </PrintLocation>
      <ObjectIDs>
         <ObjectID IDOrigin="PQ">
            <DOCID>2021956491</DOCID>
         </ObjectID>
         <ObjectID IDOrigin="PQ">
            <PCID>51894751</PCID>
         </ObjectID>
         <ObjectID IDOrigin="PQ">
            <PMID>7631</PMID>
         </ObjectID>
         <ObjectID>
            <ProvJournalCode>USA</ProvJournalCode>
         </ObjectID>
         <ObjectID IDOrigin="DTI">
            <PublisherXID>USAT30906817</PublisherXID>
         </ObjectID>
      </ObjectIDs>
      <LexileScore>1350</LexileScore>
      <Contributors>
         <Contributor ContribOrder="1">
            <Author>
               <NormalizedDisplayForm>Anonymous</NormalizedDisplayForm>
               <ContribPersonNameAtt IsNormalized="true" ContribOrigin="AuthorNormalization">
                  <ContribPersonName>Anonymous</ContribPersonName>
               </ContribPersonNameAtt>
               <LastNameAtt IsNormalized="true" ContribOrigin="AuthorNormalization">
                  <LastName>Anonymous</LastName>
               </LastNameAtt>
               <OriginalFormAtt ContribOrigin="pqauth">
                  <OriginalForm>Anonymous</OriginalForm>
               </OriginalFormAtt>
            </Author>
         </Contributor>
      </Contributors>
      <LegacyDataMapping>
         <MappingVersion>$Header: /builds/sis990002/sis/gs40/RCS/gs51.xslt,v 2.5 2015/12/02 19:41:05 azastrow Exp $</MappingVersion>
      </LegacyDataMapping>
   </Obj>
   <TextInfo>
      <Text WordCount="886" HTMLContent="true">&lt;html&gt;            &lt;head&gt;              &lt;meta name="ValidationSchema" content="http://www.w3.org/2002/08/xhtml/xhtml1-strict.xsd"/&gt;              &lt;title&gt; &lt;/title&gt;            &lt;/head&gt;            &lt;body&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Arizona: RHP Dan Haren has a three-start hitting streak, during which he is 6-for-9 with a double, a run and an RBI. He is hitting .429 (6-for-14) in five games this season. Haren's fourth-inning single Monday was the last hit for the Diamondbacks in their 5-3 victory against Colorado.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Atlanta: SS Yunel Escobar is the latest player to get a tryout in the leadoff spot, batting atop the order the last two days. He was 1-for-4 with a walk Monday. Through the weekend, Braves leadoff hitters had a big-league-worst .091 average (7-for-77) and a .165 on-base percentage.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Chicago: OF Xavier Nady has received most of his starts against left-handed pitching, but manager Lou Piniella might mix things up. "What I'd like to do with Nady, if I can, is give him a start against right-hand pitching as opposed to just lefties, because what happens, invariably, is you start pulling off the ball a little bit," Piniella said. "You face a right-hander, hitting from the right side, it makes you stay closed. I think that will help him get going."  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Cincinnati: Manager Dusty Baker shook up the lineup, dropping SS Orlando Cabrera to sixth and moving 2B Brandon Phillips up to second.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Colorado: Two-fifths of the rotation landed on the 15-day disabled list. LHP Jorge De La Rosa is out with a torn tendon in his left middle finger; RHP Jason Hammel is sidelined with a right groin strain. RHP Jhoulys Chacin and RH reliever Juan Rincon were promoted from Class AAA Colorado Springs, and Chacin will start in De La Rosa's turn Saturday at San Francisco. ...The opening-day catcher, Chris Iannetta, was optioned to Colorado Springs after batting .133 (4-for-30) in eight games. His only two RBI came on solo homers. C Paul Phillips had his contract purchased from Colorado Springs to serve as Miguel Olivo's backup. Phillips hit .311 in 17 games with the Rockies last season.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Florida: RF Cody Ross was scratched from the starting lineup an hour before game time because of flu-like symptoms. He went 2-for-3 Monday but left that game in the sixth inning to rest his left foot, which was hit by a foul ball the previous day.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Houston: 1B Lance Berkman, who hyperextended his right knee in his last at-bat Sunday, was back in the lineup for the series opener against Cincinnati. It was the same knee on which Berkman had arthroscopic surgery during spring training, forcing him to miss the start of the season.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Los Angeles: RHP Vicente Padilla was diagnosed with an irritated radial nerve in his right forearm after undergoing an MRI, and he won't try throwing for seven to 10 days. Padilla, the Dodgers' opening-day starter, went on the DL last weekend. The team doesn't have a timetable for his return.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Milwaukee: LHP Chris Capuano, who pitched for the Brewers before having a second reconstructive elbow surgery in May 2008, has been assigned to high-A Brevard County (Viera, Fla.) to continue his comeback attempt. Capuano made a few appearances in the Brewers' camp before staying behind in extended spring training to build arm strength.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;New York: Daniel Murphy, the incumbent first baseman until he sprained his right knee during the final week of spring training, has begun swinging in the batting cage. The team has not announced a timetable for his return.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Philadelphia: RHP Kyle Kendrick's turn in the rotation would come in the series opener against the Mets on Friday, but he is winless in four starts with a 7.71 ERA.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Pittsburgh: RHP Jeff Karstens became the eighth different starter used by the Pirates this season when he pitched at Milwaukee after having his contract purchased from Class AAA Indianapolis. The last time the Pirates used eight starters within the first 20 games of a season was 1953.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;St. Louis: Manager Tony La Russa, in an attempt to get his offense going -- slumping SS Brendan Ryan, in particular -- batted Ryan ninth and RHP Chris Carpenter eighth. The last time La Russa had hit the pitcher eighth was July 21, three days before LF Matt Holliday was acquired. ... C Jason LaRue, who had been sidelined the minimum 15 days due to a strained right hamstring, was activated from the DL. The Cardinals optioned C Bryan Anderson to Class AAA Memphis, one day after he provided a game-tying double as a pinch-hitter at Atlanta.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;San Diego: RHP Chris Young (right shoulder tightness) threw a successful bullpen session Monday with manager Bud Black in the batter's box to better evaluate every pitch. Young will make a rehab start for Class AAA Portland (Ore.) at Salt Lake City on Thursday.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;San Francisco: CF Aaron Rowand is eligible to come off the 15-day DL Sunday, and manager Bruce Bochy said that'll likely be the day he'll be activated. Rowand was shelved after getting beaned and sustaining cheekbone fractures and a concussion.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;Washington: RH reliever Brian Bruney has been struggling with his control. He walked three in 1a" innings Monday, giving him 12 walks in 9a" innings this year. His four-pitch walk to Cubs 3B Aramis Ramirez in the 10th inning forced home the winning run.  &lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;From The Sports Xchange&lt;/p&gt;            &lt;/body&gt;          &lt;/html&gt;</Text>
   </TextInfo>
   <DFS>
      <PubFrosting>
         <Title>USA TODAY</Title>
         <MpubId>15008</MpubId>
         <SortTitle>USA TODAY</SortTitle>
         <Qualifier>McLean, Va.</Qualifier>
         <JournalCode>USA</JournalCode>
         <SourceType>Newspapers</SourceType>
         <StartDate>19820101</StartDate>
         <EndDate>99991231</EndDate>
         <publisher>
            <PublisherName>USA Today, a division of Gannett Satellite Information Network, Inc.</PublisherName>
            <PublisherAddress>
               <Address1>7950 Jones Branch Drive</Address1>
               <City>MacLean</City>
               <Province>VA</Province>
               <ZipCode>22108</ZipCode>
               <Country>United States</Country>
            </PublisherAddress>
            <URL>http://www.usatoday.com/</URL>
         </publisher>
         <Locators>
            <Locator Type="PQPMID">
               <Name>7631</Name>
            </Locator>
            <Locator Type="ISSN">
               <Name>07347456</Name>
            </Locator>
         </Locators>
         <CatalogNum>60430.00</CatalogNum>
         <Languages>
            <Language>eng</Language>
         </Languages>
         <Flags>
            <Flag Type="BLOCK_BY_PUB">N</Flag>
            <Flag Type="ARTICLE_TRANSLATION">Y</Flag>
            <Flag Type="ALERTING_FLAG">Y</Flag>
            <Flag Type="DOC_USAGE_ROYALTIES">N</Flag>
            <Flag Type="UNSTRUCTURED_DATA">N</Flag>
            <Flag Type="PRIMARY_SOURCE_FLAG">N</Flag>
            <Flag Type="OPEN_LAYER_RIGHTS">OL_IN_NONE</Flag>
            <Flag Type="OL_CRAWL_BLOCKED">Y</Flag>
            <Flag Type="EXCLUDE_FROM_TDM">N</Flag>
            <Flag Type="EXCLUDE_FROM_GOOGLE_SCHOLAR">N</Flag>
            <Flag Type="INCLUDE_IN_PAC">N</Flag>
         </Flags>
         <Subjects>
            <Subject>General Interest Periodicals--United States</Subject>
         </Subjects>
         <CurrentTitle>
            <Title>USA TODAY</Title>
            <SortTitle>USA TODAY</SortTitle>
            <Qualifier>McLean, Va.</Qualifier>
            <EndIssueDate>99991231</EndIssueDate>
            <Locators>
               <Locator Type="PQPMID">
                  <Name>7631</Name>
               </Locator>
               <Locator Type="ISSN">
                  <Name>07347456</Name>
               </Locator>
            </Locators>
            <CatalogNum>60430.00</CatalogNum>
         </CurrentTitle>
         
         <CoverImageType>None</CoverImageType>
         <BrowseType>IssueDateBrowse</BrowseType>
         <EmbargoDays>0</EmbargoDays>
         <HasGaps>0</HasGaps>
         <CoverageRange>
            <AlphaStartDate>Jan 2, 1989</AlphaStartDate>
            <AlphaEndDate>Current</AlphaEndDate>
            <NumericStartDate>19890102</NumericStartDate>
            <NumericEndDate>99990101</NumericEndDate>
         </CoverageRange>
         <PubFrequencies/>
         <ContentModel>CM_DEFAULT</ContentModel>
      </PubFrosting>
      <GroupFrosting>
         <AlphaDate>Apr 28, 2010</AlphaDate>
         <StartDate>2010-04-28</StartDate>
         <EndDate>2010-04-28</EndDate>
         <Locators>
            <Locator Type="PQPCID">
               <Name>51894751</Name>
            </Locator>
         </Locators>
      </GroupFrosting>
      
   </DFS>
   
</RECORD>