<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RECORD>
<GOID>409032685</GOID>
<Obj>
<SourceRollupType>Newspapers</SourceRollupType>
<ObjectTypes>
<other ObjectTypeOrigin="Publisher">News</other>
<mstar>News</mstar>
</ObjectTypes>
<ObjectRollupType>Articles - All Types</ObjectRollupType>
<TitleAtt>
<Title>A cloud looms over the Grand Canyon Skywalk ; Tribal leaders see a bridge to an economic future; opponents see a sacrilege</Title>
</TitleAtt>
<SubTitleAtt>
<SubTitle>[FINAL Edition]</SubTitle>
</SubTitleAtt>
<NumericDate>2007-03-16</NumericDate>
<StartDate>2007-03-16</StartDate>
<EndDate>2007-03-16</EndDate>
<AlphaDate>Mar 16, 2007</AlphaDate>
<PageCount>0</PageCount>
<Language>
<RawLang>English</RawLang>
</Language>
<Language IsPrimary="true">
<ISO>
<ISOCode>ENG</ISOCode>
<ISOExpansion ISOCode="ENG">English</ISOExpansion>
</ISO>
</Language>
<Copyright>
<CopyrightData>(Copyright (c) 2007 USA Today. All Rights Reserved.)</CopyrightData>
</Copyright>
<PrintLocation>
<StartPage>A.1</StartPage>
<Pagination>A.1</Pagination>
<DocSection>NEWS</DocSection>
<ColumnHeader>Cover story</ColumnHeader>
</PrintLocation>
<ObjectIDs>
<ObjectID IDOrigin="PQ">
<DOCID>1234879901</DOCID>
</ObjectID>
<ObjectID IDOrigin="PQ">
<PCID>35262811</PCID>
</ObjectID>
<ObjectID IDOrigin="PQ">
<PMID>7631</PMID>
</ObjectID>
<ObjectID>
<ProvJournalCode>USA</ProvJournalCode>
</ObjectID>
<ObjectID IDOrigin="DTI">
<PublisherXID>USAT14949662</PublisherXID>
</ObjectID>
</ObjectIDs>
<LexileScore>1380</LexileScore>
<Contributors>
<Contributor ContribOrder="1">
<Author>
<NormalizedDisplayForm>Clark, Jayne</NormalizedDisplayForm>
<LastNameAtt ContribOrigin="AuthorNormalization" IsNormalized="true">
<LastName>Clark</LastName>
</LastNameAtt>
<FirstNameAtt ContribOrigin="AuthorNormalization" IsNormalized="true">
<FirstName>Jayne</FirstName>
</FirstNameAtt>
<OriginalFormAtt ContribOrigin="pqauth">
<OriginalForm>Jayne Clark</OriginalForm>
</OriginalFormAtt>
</Author>
</Contributor>
</Contributors>
<Terms>
<CompanyTerm PndxHeader="true" TermSource="NA">
<CompanyNameAtt>
<CompanyName>Hualapai Tribe</CompanyName>
</CompanyNameAtt>
<CompanyNAICAtt>
<CompanyNAIC>921150</CompanyNAIC>
</CompanyNAICAtt>
</CompanyTerm>
<GenSubjTerm PndxHeader="true" TermSource="ABI">
<GenSubjValue>Native North Americans</GenSubjValue>
</GenSubjTerm>
<GenSubjTerm PndxHeader="true" TermSource="ABI">
<GenSubjValue>National parks</GenSubjValue>
</GenSubjTerm>
<GenSubjTerm PndxHeader="true" TermSource="NA">
<GenSubjValue>Tourist attractions</GenSubjValue>
</GenSubjTerm>
<GenSubjTerm PndxHeader="true" TermSource="NA">
<GenSubjValue>Walkways</GenSubjValue>
</GenSubjTerm>
<Term PndxHeader="true" TermSource="ABI">
<Geographic>Grand Canyon</Geographic>
</Term>
</Terms>
<Abstract>
<Short WordCount="176">
<AbsText HTMLContent="true">          &lt;html&gt;            &lt;head&gt;              &lt;meta name="ValidationSchema" content="http://www.w3.org/2002/08/xhtml/xhtml1-strict.xsd"/&gt;              &lt;title&gt; &lt;/title&gt;            &lt;/head&gt;            &lt;body&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Skywalk is the centerpiece of Grand Canyon West, the 9,000-acre swath of the 1 million-acre Hualapai (WALL-a-pie) Reservation set aside for tourist development. Plans call for a 6,000-square-foot visitors center at the entrance of the platform with a high-end restaurant, museum, movie theater and meeting space.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   At Eagle Point near the Skywalk, greeter Don Havatone, brother of Janette Havatone, is resplendent in a homemade feathered headdress. He guides visitors to the edge of the 4,000-foot abyss, which, unlike the glass-sided Skywalk, is unfettered by guardrails.  He swears they haven't lost anyone yet.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Basic admission to Grand Canyon West is $49.95, which includes a buffet lunch and access to a small collection of attractions on the Hualapai Indian Reservation at the canyon's western edge. A 15- minute visit to the Skywalk costs an additional $25. Attractions include a village of several traditional Indian dwellings and an Old West replica village. Add-on horseback rides and Hummer tours start at $59 each. Helicopter tours into the canyon with a pontoon boat ride on the Colorado River are $149.&lt;/p&gt;            &lt;/body&gt;          &lt;/html&gt;</AbsText>
</Short>
</Abstract>
<LegacyDataMapping>
<MappingVersion>$Header: /builds/sis990002/sis/gs40/RCS/gs51.xslt,v 2.5 2015/12/02 19:41:05 azastrow Exp $</MappingVersion>
</LegacyDataMapping>
</Obj>
<TextInfo>
<Text HTMLContent="true" WordCount="1654">&lt;html&gt;            &lt;head&gt;              &lt;meta name="ValidationSchema" content="http://www.w3.org/2002/08/xhtml/xhtml1-strict.xsd"/&gt;              &lt;title&gt; &lt;/title&gt;            &lt;/head&gt;            &lt;body&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   GRAND CANYON WEST, Ariz. -- Janette Havatone gazes at the peach- colored, glass-bottomed viewing platform being nudged into position 4,000 feet above the Grand Canyon's floor on her native Hualapai Indian Reservation and recalls how she wept when she first heard of plans to build the structure.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   "You got a natural peace when you were out here, and that's gone," says Havatone, 51, a teacher turned gift shop clerk. But she's philosophical now about the tourist attraction. Her tribe, she says, is "moving from the natural into a new era."&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Tribal officials look at the new Grand Canyon Skywalk that juts 65 feet off the rim into thin air and see economic survival. Some conservationists, however, view it as a tacky tourist attraction that defaces a natural wonder.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   The much-hyped $30 million Skywalk will give tourists with steely nerves and $74.95 to spare a bird's-eye view of the canyon below when it opens March 28. But already, Skywalk has been dubbed everything from inspired to blasphemous.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   "I still believe in the old ways," Havatone says. "But this sets us up for the future. My children and grandchildren will have something to fall back on" economically.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   On Monday, three years after construction began on the million- pound platform, members of the impoverished Hualapai tribe will walk out onto the horseshoe-shaped deck for the first time. Former astronaut Buzz Aldrin leads a ceremonial "first walk" Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   The soaring walkway is certainly the Hualapai's most out-there tourist endeavor, though it isn't their first. Or their last.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Skywalk is the centerpiece of Grand Canyon West, the 9,000-acre swath of the 1 million-acre Hualapai (WALL-a-pie) Reservation set aside for tourist development. Plans call for a 6,000-square-foot visitors center at the entrance of the platform with a high-end restaurant, museum, movie theater and meeting space.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   A long-term $45 million airport expansion at Grand Canyon West to accommodate larger aircraft is underway. Forty cabin-style rooms are planned, and some of them are open. Off-road turf for Hummer tours is being expanded. A resort hotel may eventually take shape. And perhaps most audaciously, the tribe is considering running a tram from the rim to the canyon floor.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Far from the national park&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   The Hualapai's location at the far western reaches of the 277- mile-long canyon and about 250 road miles west of the major tourist facilities at Grand Canyon National Park's South Rim means they attract only a fraction of the park's numbers.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   About 300,000 visitors a year arrive here (compared with the national park's more than 4 million), and most are on day trips from Las Vegas. Tribal officials predict the Skywalk will double attendance this year alone and say they can handle 2,000 visitors a day (up from an average of 500 on the rim), despite the lack of infrastructure such as electricity and water.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   For now, they're trucking in 8,000 gallons of water a day from 30 miles away. Waste is hauled out. Power is generated by diesel engines. And getting into the park requires a 14-mile drive over unpaved, washboard roads.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Not all the Hualapai's previous ventures have had happy endings. A casino built in the mid-'90s folded after only seven months -- the first Arizona Indian gaming operation to do so. Turns out, visitors, most of whom were fresh from the glitz of Las Vegas 120 miles west of here, had little desire to jerk slots handles in a gloomy airport terminal when the wondrous Grand Canyon loomed nearby.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Similarly, a proposed "scientific Disneyland" featuring telescopes for night-sky viewing never got off the ground. In 1999, the tribe allowed daredevil Robbie Knievel to jump a side canyon on his motorcycle, a feat that garnered intense, though fleeting, attention.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Baby steps for tourism&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   The tribe's first foray into tourism came in the 1970s when it began offering rafting trips on the Colorado River. Today, about 6,000 people a year run the river. They arrive by vehicle on the only road into the canyon 18 miles downhill from the tribal headquarters at Peach Springs and are lifted out by helicopter.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Later, the tribe partnered with other operators to run combination sightseeing flights and pontoon boat rides. New in the past two years are a rimside Indian village, featuring replica native dwellings of several tribes, and a faux Old West town with cowboys, but notably, no Indians.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   The Grand Canyon West experience is at once free-form and scripted. Visitors who haven't flown in on a package deal park their vehicles near a sign warning of low-flying aircraft at the small airport terminal and take shuttle buses to the attractions.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Drivers make standard wisecracks about "Grand Canyon divorces" ("Step back a little farther, honey ..."), and the same gunfight plays over and over in the dusty Old West plaza. At the Indian village, Native American dancers in native dress -- though not necessarily that of their own tribes -- perform for tips.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   At Eagle Point near the Skywalk, greeter Don Havatone, brother of Janette Havatone, is resplendent in a homemade feathered headdress. He guides visitors to the edge of the 4,000-foot abyss, which, unlike the glass-sided Skywalk, is unfettered by guardrails.  He swears they haven't lost anyone yet.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   As a sovereign nation, the Hualapai aren't bound by National Park Service regulations. This is the only spot in the Grand Canyon where helicopters can fly below the rim, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   There are no park rangers, though there is a security guard who threatened spectators with expulsion last week for snapping photos of tribal officials and business associates walking on the newly rolled-out Skywalk.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   (The tribe is saving the photo opportunities for Tuesday ceremonies with Aldrin.)&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   'Tacky, gross, commercial'&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Meanwhile, this latest attraction has sparked apoplexy among some environmentalists.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Though he understands the Hualapai's need for economic development, "The tribe has repeatedly brought tacky, gross commercial ventures into the canyon, and it's inappropriate. Especially when there are alternatives," says Kieran Suckling, policy director for the Tucson-based Center for Biological Diversity.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   "We're frankly aghast at what they're doing to the Grand Canyon. It's one of the seven wonders of the world, and they're making it a Disneyland."&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Some tribal elders also express concern. One octogenarian, who didn't want her name used for fear of retribution, says the Skywalk violates long-held beliefs that the land should be respected.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Tribal leaders counter that they're developing only a fraction of that land. Having opted out of gaming, a $23billion-a-year industry for Native American tribes elsewhere, the Hualapai looked for something to generate revenue and saw their slice of the Grand Canyon as a natural.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   "For us to take a small portion is nothing compared to what's going on outside," says Robert Bravo Jr., operations manager for Grand Canyon West. "We're sitting on one of the seven natural wonders of the world. We have all kinds of goals and visions."&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Sheri Yellowhawk, 37, a mother of six who earned her master's degree online, has directed the tribe's economic ventures for the past five years. With unemployment at about 50% and more than a third of the tribe's 1,400 on-reservation members living below the poverty level, economic development is a priority, she says.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Sipping a Rockstar energy drink near the Skywalk last week, she defended the business partnerships that have ramped up commercial enterprises during her tenure. "We're not building a power plant. We're building a natural way to view the canyon," she says.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   The Skywalk was the brainchild of China-born Las Vegas businessman David Jin, whose tourism-related dealings with the tribe date to the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Originally, the walkway was conceived as a more-humble $200,000 platform, Yellowhawk says, and evolved into a more ambitious 70- foot-long by 65-foot-wide sky bridge.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Jin and the Hualapai will share the profits for a period, but the tribe ultimately will own the attraction.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   "Change is hard, but we have to prepare for the future," Yellowhawk says. "I don't think the Skywalk will save us. But it's a catalyst."&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   TEXT OF INFO BOX BEGINS HERE&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   If you want to go skywalking&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   *Getting there: Grand Canyon West is about 120 miles east of Las Vegas and 250 miles west of Grand Canyon National Park's main entrance. Day tours that include flights from Las Vegas are available.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   *Skywalk and other attractions: The Grand Canyon Skywalk opens to the public March 28 after an invitation-only opening Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   Basic admission to Grand Canyon West is $49.95, which includes a buffet lunch and access to a small collection of attractions on the Hualapai Indian Reservation at the canyon's western edge. A 15- minute visit to the Skywalk costs an additional $25. Attractions include a village of several traditional Indian dwellings and an Old West replica village. Add-on horseback rides and Hummer tours start at $59 each. Helicopter tours into the canyon with a pontoon boat ride on the Colorado River are $149.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   The Hualapais also operate day-long river-rafting trips now through October, departing from  headquarters in Peach Springs on old Route 66 (and about 60 miles by dirt road from Grand Canyon West) for $328, including transportation into the canyon and a helicopter transfer out.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   *Where to stay: Lodging in Peach Springs is at the tribe-owned 59- room Hualapai Lodge. Rates: $79.95-$99.95, depending on season. At Grand Canyon West, 40 rooms will be available later this year, only as part of package deals.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;p&gt;   *Information: 877-716-9378; destinationgrandcanyon.com.&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;div&gt;&lt;object class="mstar_text_entity"&gt;&lt;param name="pq_source" value="csx"/&gt;&lt;param name="pq_etype" value="41"/&gt;&lt;param name="mstar_entity_inline" value="N"/&gt;&lt;param name="mstar_entity_type" value="Illustration"/&gt;&lt;div class="Illustration_content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;GRAPHIC, B/W, Skywalk rendering: Daniel Bentley, Lochsa Engineering; graphic by Dave Merrill and Adrienne Lewis, USA TODAY, Sources: Skywalk, USA TODAY research (Diagrams, map); PHOTO, Color, Brian Jones, Las Vegas News Bureau, via Getty Images; PHOTO, B/W&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/object&gt;&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;/body&gt;          &lt;/html&gt;</Text>
</TextInfo>
<DFS>
<PubFrosting>
<Title>USA TODAY</Title>
<MpubId>15008</MpubId>
<SortTitle>USA TODAY</SortTitle>
<Qualifier>McLean, Va.</Qualifier>
<JournalCode>USA</JournalCode>
<SourceType>Newspapers</SourceType>
<StartDate>19820101</StartDate>
<EndDate>99991231</EndDate>
<publisher>
<PublisherName>USA Today, a division of Gannett Satellite Information Network, Inc.</PublisherName>
<PublisherAddress>
<Address1>7950 Jones Branch Drive</Address1>
<City>MacLean</City>
<Province>VA</Province>
<ZipCode>22108</ZipCode>
<Country>United States</Country>
</PublisherAddress>
<URL>http://www.usatoday.com/</URL>
</publisher>
<Locators>
<Locator Type="PQPMID">
<Name>7631</Name>
</Locator>
<Locator Type="ISSN">
<Name>07347456</Name>
</Locator>
</Locators>
<CatalogNum>60430.00</CatalogNum>
<Languages>
<Language>eng</Language>
</Languages>
<Flags>
<Flag Type="BLOCK_BY_PUB">N</Flag>
<Flag Type="ARTICLE_TRANSLATION">Y</Flag>
<Flag Type="ALERTING_FLAG">Y</Flag>
<Flag Type="DOC_USAGE_ROYALTIES">N</Flag>
<Flag Type="UNSTRUCTURED_DATA">N</Flag>
<Flag Type="PRIMARY_SOURCE_FLAG">N</Flag>
<Flag Type="OPEN_LAYER_RIGHTS">OL_IN_NONE</Flag>
<Flag Type="OL_CRAWL_BLOCKED">Y</Flag>
<Flag Type="EXCLUDE_FROM_TDM">N</Flag>
<Flag Type="EXCLUDE_FROM_GOOGLE_SCHOLAR">N</Flag>
<Flag Type="INCLUDE_IN_PAC">N</Flag>
</Flags>
<Subjects>
<Subject>General Interest Periodicals--United States</Subject>
</Subjects>
<CurrentTitle>
<Title>USA TODAY</Title>
<SortTitle>USA TODAY</SortTitle>
<Qualifier>McLean, Va.</Qualifier>
<EndIssueDate>99991231</EndIssueDate>
<Locators>
<Locator Type="PQPMID">
<Name>7631</Name>
</Locator>
<Locator Type="ISSN">
<Name>07347456</Name>
</Locator>
</Locators>
<CatalogNum>60430.00</CatalogNum>
</CurrentTitle>
<CoverImageType>None</CoverImageType>
<BrowseType>IssueDateBrowse</BrowseType>
<EmbargoDays>0</EmbargoDays>
<HasGaps>0</HasGaps>
<CoverageRange>
<AlphaStartDate>Jan 2, 1989</AlphaStartDate>
<AlphaEndDate>Current</AlphaEndDate>
<NumericStartDate>19890102</NumericStartDate>
<NumericEndDate>99990101</NumericEndDate>
</CoverageRange>
<PubFrequencies/>
<ContentModel>CM_DEFAULT</ContentModel>
</PubFrosting>
<GroupFrosting>
<AlphaDate>Mar 16, 2007</AlphaDate>
<StartDate>2007-03-16</StartDate>
<EndDate>2007-03-16</EndDate>
<Locators>
<Locator Type="PQPCID">
<Name>35262811</Name>
</Locator>
</Locators>
</GroupFrosting>
</DFS>
<grades><is_economic>1</is_economic><text_blob_sentiment>0.137178069515026</text_blob_sentiment><bert_sentiment>0.263082074082416</bert_sentiment></grades>
<processed>
<is_economic>0.7198</is_economic>
<tf_idf>[('skywalk', 0.4879), ('canyon', 0.4413), ('hualapai', 0.3691), ('tribe', 0.2228), ('grand', 0.2053), ('havatone', 0.183), ('west', 0.1241), ('yellowhawk', 0.1066), ('tribal', 0.0987), ('rim', 0.0842), ('indian', 0.0796), ('vegas', 0.0783), ('las', 0.0781), ('tourist', 0.0757), ('visitors', 0.0734), ('peach', 0.0728), ('says', 0.0705), ('miles', 0.0701), ('reservation', 0.0682), ('attractions', 0.0662), ('park', 0.0657), ('natural', 0.0651), ('attraction', 0.0625), ('tacky', 0.0618), ('native', 0.0573), ('tours', 0.0573), ('000', 0.0568), ('platform', 0.0537), ('tribes', 0.0534), ('ventures', 0.0492), ('pontoon', 0.0488), ('aldrin', 0.0482), ('janette', 0.048), ('helicopter', 0.0459), ('95', 0.0456), ('village', 0.0452), ('river', 0.045), ('rafting', 0.0449), ('springs', 0.0429), ('hummer', 0.0419), ('dwellings', 0.041), ('walkway', 0.04), ('trips', 0.0397), ('economic', 0.0388), ('jin', 0.0388), ('foot', 0.0379), ('disneyland', 0.0368), ('23billion', 0.0366), ('airport', 0.0363), ('road', 0.036), ('replica', 0.0358), ('lochsa', 0.0355), ('destinationgrandcanyon', 0.0355), ('gaming', 0.0343), ('commercial', 0.0341), ('national', 0.0338), ('parkthe', 0.0337), ('million', 0.0336), ('skywalking', 0.0333), ('terminal', 0.0323), ('wonders', 0.0317), ('fraction', 0.0316), ('old', 0.0312), ('defaces', 0.0309), ('tourism', 0.0306), ('viewing', 0.0301), ('rides', 0.03), ('long', 0.0298), ('development', 0.0291), ('apoplexy', 0.029), ('day', 0.0289), ('view', 0.0288), ('9378', 0.0287), ('gross', 0.0284), ('flights', 0.0284), ('aircraft', 0.0282), ('entrance', 0.0281), ('boat', 0.0279), ('acre', 0.0273), ('arrive', 0.0267), ('sky', 0.0263), ('120', 0.0263), ('knievel', 0.0261), ('audaciously', 0.0261), ('washboard', 0.0253), ('headquarters', 0.0253), ('package', 0.0251), ('featuring', 0.0251), ('suckling', 0.025), ('colorado', 0.025), ('rooms', 0.0249), ('rockstar', 0.0249), ('greeter', 0.0247), ('near', 0.0246), ('59', 0.0246), ('opens', 0.0245), ('seven', 0.0245), ('blasphemous', 0.024), ('juts', 0.0239), ('glass', 0.0238), ('250', 0.0237), ('unpaved', 0.0237), ('mile', 0.0235), ('wisecracks', 0.0235), ('small', 0.0234), ('headdress', 0.0233), ('graphic', 0.0231), ('edge', 0.023), ('kieran', 0.023), ('guardrails', 0.023), ('tuesday', 0.0228), ('octogenarian', 0.0228), ('65', 0.0227), ('resplendent', 0.0227), ('gazes', 0.0226), ('gunfight', 0.0224), ('tram', 0.0222), ('diagrams', 0.0222), ('year', 0.0221), ('daredevil', 0.022), ('telescopes', 0.0219), ('aghast', 0.0218), ('divorces', 0.0217), ('716', 0.0216), ('officials', 0.0216), ('compared', 0.0214), ('glitz', 0.0214), ('feathered', 0.0213), ('sheri', 0.0212), ('today', 0.0212), ('conservationists', 0.0211), ('bottomed', 0.0211), ('haven', 0.0211), ('swears', 0.021), ('horseshoe', 0.021), ('western', 0.0209), ('floor', 0.0207), ('walk', 0.0207), ('land', 0.0206), ('nudged', 0.0205), ('wondrous', 0.0205), ('abyss', 0.0205), ('sightseeing', 0.0203), ('endings', 0.0202), ('brainchild', 0.0201), ('ramped', 0.0201), ('steely', 0.02), ('unfettered', 0.0198), ('feet', 0.0197), ('loomed', 0.0197), ('usa', 0.0197), ('bentley', 0.0196), ('expulsion', 0.0196), ('wept', 0.0195), ('trucking', 0.0194), ('hyped', 0.0194), ('horseback', 0.0194), ('328', 0.019), ('gloomy', 0.019), ('water', 0.0188), ('astronaut', 0.0188), ('retribution', 0.0187), ('28', 0.0187), ('adrienne', 0.0187), ('foray', 0.0187), ('277', 0.0187), ('partnered', 0.0185), ('sipping', 0.0184), ('hauled', 0.0183), ('jerk', 0.0183), ('sovereign', 0.0182), ('scripted', 0.0182), ('robbie', 0.0182), ('fleeting', 0.0182), ('bravo', 0.0181), ('elders', 0.0181), ('available', 0.0181), ('ceremonial', 0.018), ('snapping', 0.018), ('catalyst', 0.018), ('downhill', 0.0179), ('rendering', 0.0178), ('photo', 0.0178), ('lodging', 0.0177), ('tucson', 0.0177), ('swath', 0.0177), ('endeavor', 0.0177), ('march', 0.0176), ('violates', 0.0176), ('diesel', 0.0176), ('buffet', 0.0176), ('building', 0.0175), ('garnered', 0.0174), ('slots', 0.0174), ('877', 0.0174), ('departing', 0.0174), ('149', 0.0174), ('philosophical', 0.0173), ('future', 0.0173), ('faux', 0.0173), ('folded', 0.0173), ('nerves', 0.0173), ('plans', 0.0172), ('dealings', 0.0172), ('impoverished', 0.0172), ('include', 0.0171), ('visions', 0.0171), ('gallons', 0.017), ('environmentalists', 0.0169), ('lodge', 0.0169), ('merrill', 0.0168), ('partnerships', 0.0168), ('ceremonies', 0.0167), ('spectators', 0.0166), ('power', 0.0166), ('enterprises', 0.0166), ('economically', 0.0165), ('shuttle', 0.0165), ('helicopters', 0.0164), ('centerpiece', 0.0164), ('guides', 0.0164), ('conceived', 0.0164), ('flown', 0.0164), ('feat', 0.0164), ('sided', 0.0163), ('homemade', 0.0163), ('motorcycle', 0.0163), ('humble', 0.0163), ('cabin', 0.0163), ('dusty', 0.0163), ('honey', 0.016), ('engines', 0.016), ('casino', 0.0159), ('biological', 0.0159), ('began', 0.0159), ('handles', 0.0159), ('getting', 0.0158), ('pie', 0.0158), ('beliefs', 0.0157), ('turf', 0.0157), ('slice', 0.0156), ('evolved', 0.0156), ('members', 0.0155), ('eagle', 0.0155), ('inappropriate', 0.0155), ('dancers', 0.0155), ('frankly', 0.0154), ('invitation', 0.0154), ('farther', 0.0154), ('opted', 0.0154), ('dubbed', 0.0153), ('soaring', 0.0152), ('clerk', 0.0152), ('alternatives', 0.0152), ('ariz', 0.0152), ('operators', 0.0152), ('business', 0.0151), ('cowboys', 0.0151), ('buses', 0.015), ('years', 0.015), ('reaches', 0.0149), ('businessman', 0.0149), ('buzz', 0.0149), ('spare', 0.0149), ('respected', 0.0148), ('90s', 0.0148), ('predict', 0.0148), ('deck', 0.0148), ('underway', 0.0148), ('far', 0.0148), ('understands', 0.0148), ('indians', 0.0147), ('survival', 0.0147), ('past', 0.0147), ('notably', 0.0147), ('accommodate', 0.0146), ('rangers', 0.0146), ('dirt', 0.0146), ('sparked', 0.0146), ('tourists', 0.0146), ('later', 0.0146), ('grandchildren', 0.0144), ('electricity', 0.0144), ('run', 0.0144), ('plaza', 0.0144), ('attendance', 0.0144), ('tenure', 0.0144), ('diversity', 0.0143), ('colored', 0.0143), ('lifted', 0.0142), ('defended', 0.0141), ('bird', 0.014), ('generate', 0.014), ('scientific', 0.014), ('unemployment', 0.014), ('got', 0.014), ('recalls', 0.014), ('engineering', 0.0139), ('similarly', 0.0139), ('poverty', 0.0139), ('resort', 0.0138), ('generated', 0.0138), ('ambitious', 0.0138), ('shaped', 0.0138), ('center', 0.0137), ('waste', 0.0137), ('associates', 0.0137), ('rolled', 0.0137), ('admission', 0.0136), ('infrastructure', 0.0136), ('profits', 0.0136), ('attract', 0.0136), ('79', 0.0135), ('saving', 0.0135), ('tips', 0.0135), ('bound', 0.0134), ('dress', 0.0134), ('little', 0.0134), ('american', 0.0133), ('depending', 0.0133), ('regulations', 0.0133), ('new', 0.0133), ('74', 0.0133), ('30', 0.0132), ('transfer', 0.0132), ('drivers', 0.0132), ('counter', 0.0132), ('operate', 0.0131), ('drink', 0.0131), ('priority', 0.0131), ('roads', 0.0131), ('expansion', 0.013), ('want', 0.013), ('portion', 0.013), ('1970s', 0.013), ('kinds', 0.0129), ('necessarily', 0.0129), ('lewis', 0.0129), ('pound', 0.0129), ('expanded', 0.0129), ('express', 0.0129), ('bureau', 0.0128), ('flying', 0.0128), ('combination', 0.0128), ('map', 0.0127), ('structure', 0.0127), ('world', 0.0127), ('lunch', 0.0127), ('info', 0.0126), ('prepare', 0.0126), ('desire', 0.0126), ('intense', 0.0126), ('66', 0.0126), ('bridge', 0.0126), ('dave', 0.0126), ('newly', 0.0126), ('developing', 0.0126), ('gift', 0.0125), ('1990s', 0.0125), ('facilities', 0.0125), ('plant', 0.0124), ('threatened', 0.0124), ('vehicles', 0.0124), ('deals', 0.0123), ('warning', 0.0123), ('jump', 0.0123), ('fly', 0.0123), ('shape', 0.0123), ('perform', 0.0122), ('99', 0.0122), ('repeatedly', 0.0121), ('week', 0.0121), ('sets', 0.012), ('operation', 0.012), ('51', 0.012), ('handle', 0.012), ('master', 0.012), ('wonder', 0.0119), ('location', 0.0119), ('instance', 0.0119), ('basic', 0.0119), ('route', 0.0119), ('teacher', 0.0119), ('aside', 0.0119), ('ride', 0.0119), ('inspired', 0.0119), ('opportunities', 0.0119), ('arizona', 0.0118), ('directed', 0.0118), ('unlike', 0.0117), ('transportation', 0.0117), ('requires', 0.0117), ('vehicle', 0.0117), ('49', 0.0117), ('don', 0.0117), ('peace', 0.0117), ('daniel', 0.0116), ('getty', 0.0116), ('shop', 0.0116), ('collection', 0.0116), ('considering', 0.0116), ('museum', 0.0116), ('walking', 0.0115), ('leads', 0.0115), ('sources', 0.0115), ('ultimately', 0.0115), ('baby', 0.0114), ('china', 0.0113), ('goals', 0.0113), ('steps', 0.0113), ('1999', 0.0112), ('restaurant', 0.0112), ('theater', 0.0112), ('turns', 0.0112), ('fresh', 0.0111), ('begins', 0.0111), ('degree', 0.0111), ('37', 0.0111), ('revenue', 0.0111), ('owned', 0.0111), ('sitting', 0.0111), ('hotel', 0.0111), ('offering', 0.0111), ('nearby', 0.011), ('rates', 0.011), ('construction', 0.011), ('standard', 0.011), ('text', 0.011), ('earned', 0.011), ('eye', 0.0109), ('concern', 0.0109), ('jones', 0.0109), ('larger', 0.0109), ('operations', 0.0109), ('box', 0.0108), ('traditional', 0.0108), ('brian', 0.0108), ('proposed', 0.0108), ('fear', 0.0108), ('400', 0.0107), ('images', 0.0107), ('october', 0.0106), ('guard', 0.0106), ('date', 0.0106), ('mid', 0.0106), ('square', 0.0106), ('lack', 0.0106), ('era', 0.0106), ('planned', 0.0105), ('photos', 0.0105), ('save', 0.0105), ('spot', 0.0105), ('add', 0.0104), ('originally', 0.0104), ('70', 0.0104), ('energy', 0.0104), ('eventually', 0.0104), ('certainly', 0.0104), ('brother', 0.0104), ('wide', 0.0104), ('aren', 0.0103), ('additional', 0.0103), ('access', 0.0103), ('300', 0.0103), ('related', 0.0102), ('minute', 0.0102), ('movie', 0.0102), ('happy', 0.0102), ('born', 0.0102), ('online', 0.0102), ('costs', 0.0101), ('looked', 0.0101), ('numbers', 0.0101), ('wall', 0.0101), ('plays', 0.0101), ('double', 0.01), ('form', 0.01), ('jr', 0.01), ('build', 0.01), ('visit', 0.0099), ('style', 0.0099), ('previous', 0.0099), ('main', 0.0098), ('heard', 0.0098), ('45', 0.0098), ('built', 0.0098), ('moving', 0.0098), ('period', 0.0097), ('ground', 0.0097), ('gone', 0.0097), ('opening', 0.0097), ('space', 0.0096), ('step', 0.0096), ('latest', 0.0096), ('position', 0.0095), ('sign', 0.0095), ('200', 0.0095), ('attention', 0.0095), ('allowed', 0.0095), ('average', 0.0094), ('industry', 0.0094), ('includes', 0.0094), ('ways', 0.0094), ('60', 0.0094), ('policy', 0.0094), ('leaders', 0.0094), ('drive', 0.0094), ('share', 0.0094), ('brought', 0.0093), ('research', 0.0093), ('town', 0.0093), ('color', 0.0093), ('term', 0.0093), ('stay', 0.0093), ('living', 0.0093), ('meeting', 0.0092), ('means', 0.0092), ('east', 0.0092), ('experience', 0.0092), ('saw', 0.0091), ('manager', 0.0091), ('robert', 0.0091), ('security', 0.009), ('level', 0.0089), ('500', 0.0089), ('air', 0.0089), ('fall', 0.0089), ('mother', 0.0088), ('isn', 0.0088), ('low', 0.0088), ('turned', 0.0087), ('especially', 0.0087), ('despite', 0.0087), ('com', 0.0087), ('believe', 0.0086), ('running', 0.0085), ('nation', 0.0085), ('deal', 0.0084), ('david', 0.0084), ('outside', 0.0084), ('40', 0.0084), ('room', 0.0084), ('information', 0.0083), ('south', 0.0083), ('held', 0.0082), ('doing', 0.0082), ('service', 0.0081), ('having', 0.008), ('18', 0.008), ('change', 0.008), ('children', 0.008), ('lost', 0.008), ('14', 0.008), ('50', 0.0079), ('major', 0.0078), ('25', 0.0078), ('free', 0.0077), ('open', 0.0076), ('hard', 0.0076), ('monday', 0.0076), ('start', 0.0076), ('director', 0.0074), ('months', 0.0074), ('news', 0.0074), ('look', 0.0074), ('making', 0.0073), ('based', 0.0073), ('away', 0.0072), ('point', 0.0072), ('season', 0.0072), ('didn', 0.0072), ('used', 0.0071), ('came', 0.0071), ('night', 0.007), ('15', 0.007), ('set', 0.007), ('need', 0.007), ('public', 0.0068), ('end', 0.0067), ('think', 0.0064), ('including', 0.0062), ('say', 0.0062), ('high', 0.0061), ('going', 0.0061), ('way', 0.0057), ('make', 0.0055), ('people', 0.0051), ('time', 0.0046)]</tf_idf>
<bert_title_negative>0.2618</bert_title_negative>
<bert_title_positive>0.7382</bert_title_positive>
<roberta_title_negative>0.9359</roberta_title_negative>
<roberta_title_neutral>0.0634</roberta_title_neutral>
<roberta_title_positive>0.0007</roberta_title_positive>
<bert_paragraph_positive>0.6326521739130435</bert_paragraph_positive>
<bert_paragraph_neutral>0.0</bert_paragraph_neutral>
<bert_paragraph_negative>0.3673478260869566</bert_paragraph_negative>

<roberta_paragraph_positive>0.0008673913043478264</roberta_paragraph_positive>

<roberta_paragraph_neutral>0.8223282608695649</roberta_paragraph_neutral>

<roberta_paragraph_negative>0.17680869565217397</roberta_paragraph_negative>
</processed>
</RECORD>